[
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Apollo moon mission was the first to carry a lunar rover vehicle?",
        "Answer": "Apollo 15"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The scientific unit LUMEN is used in the measurement of what?",
        "Answer": "Light"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which organ of the body is affected by Bright's Disease?",
        "Answer": "Kidney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the boiling point of water using the scientific kelvin scale of temperature measurement",
        "Answer": "373k - kelvins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many surfaces does a Mobius strip have?",
        "Answer": "One"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the lightest metal under standard conditions?",
        "Answer": "Lithium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many wings does a bee have?",
        "Answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of moles?",
        "Answer": "A labour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which breed of dog has breeds called Welsh, Scottish and Irish?",
        "Answer": "Terrier"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for the medical condition epistaxis?",
        "Answer": "Nose bleed"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What sort of creature is a cassowary?",
        "Answer": "A (flightless) bird"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is made using soda, lime and silica?",
        "Answer": "Glass"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the chaparral cock, a ground cuckoo native of Mexico, better known?",
        "Answer": "The Roadrunner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who created Wikipedia on the World Wide Web?",
        "Answer": "Jimmy Wales"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Common, Water and Pygmy are types of which British mammal?",
        "Answer": "Shrew"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bone in the human body that is not attached to any other bone?",
        "Answer": "The hyoid"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body would you find the Islets of Langerhans?",
        "Answer": "The pancreas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What mineral has the lowest number on the Mohs scale?",
        "Answer": "Talc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What mineral has the highest number on the Mohs scale?",
        "Answer": "Diamond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for the liquid secreted by your lacrimal glands?",
        "Answer": "Tears"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for the liquid secreted by your lacrimal glands?",
        "Answer": "Tears"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who discovered the element Oxygen?",
        "Answer": "Joseph Priestley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective name for a group of sea cucumbers?",
        "Answer": "A pickle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the body would you find an astrocyte?",
        "Answer": "The brain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are Grey Dagger, Forester and Dingy Footman species of?",
        "Answer": "Moths"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is measured on the Mohs scale?",
        "Answer": "The hardness of minerals"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which type of animals find their way home using magnetism?",
        "Answer": "Molluscs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Yuri Gagarin's space ship?",
        "Answer": "Vostok 1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The word HENNA can be made using the periodic symbols of which three elements?",
        "Answer": "(He) Helium (N) Nitrogen (Na) Sodium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the more common name for the type of bear called the Ursus Maritimus?",
        "Answer": "Polar bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the hardest natural substance?",
        "Answer": "diamond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Nephrology is the study of which internal organ?",
        "Answer": "The kidney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where on a horse do you find its poll?",
        "Answer": "Between the ears"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does MRSA stand for?",
        "Answer": "Methicillin Resistant Staphyloccocus Aureus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which spider gets its name from when the female sometimes eats the male after mating?",
        "Answer": "Black Widow Spider"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is ylang-ylang - a herb or a flower?",
        "Answer": "Flower"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body would you find Island of Reils?",
        "Answer": "The brain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From the Sun, what is the name of the nearest star?",
        "Answer": "Proxima Centauri"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the process called in which birds lose their feathers?",
        "Answer": "Moulting"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bird that is capable of seeing the colour blue?",
        "Answer": "The owl"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bird that is capable of seeing the colour blue?",
        "Answer": "The owl"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only animal that cannot jump?",
        "Answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing what does the abbreviation U.S.B. stand for?",
        "Answer": "Universal Serial Bus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the main effect of vitamin K deficiency?",
        "Answer": "Bleeding"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Used in satellite navigation, what do the initials in the term GPS stand for?",
        "Answer": "Global Positioning System"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for Arsenic?",
        "Answer": "As"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the information technology term RAM stand for?",
        "Answer": "Random Access Memory"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest internal human organ?",
        "Answer": "The liver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Little, Eurasian Eagle and Burrowing are all types of which species of bird?",
        "Answer": "Owl"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the lightest chemical element?",
        "Answer": "Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective term for a group of racoons?",
        "Answer": "A nursery"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective term for a group of racehorses?",
        "Answer": "A string of racehorses"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "To the nearest whole number, what percentage of the Earth's atmosphere is nitrogen?",
        "Answer": "78%"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the world of the internet, what do the letters HTTP stand for?",
        "Answer": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What gas do all fuels need in order to burn?",
        "Answer": "Oxygen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is the Sodium Chloride more commonly known?",
        "Answer": "Salt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sand consists of silicon and what other element?",
        "Answer": "Oxygen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the brightest star in the northern hemisphere?",
        "Answer": "Sirius"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Common, Arctic and Sooty are all varieties of which type of bird?",
        "Answer": "Tern"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Worcester Black, Arlington Pippin and Bartlett are all varieties of which type of fruit?",
        "Answer": "Pear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body would you find the scaphoid bone?",
        "Answer": "In the wrist"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The does the chemical symbol Pb stand for?",
        "Answer": "Lead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many stomachs does a cow have?",
        "Answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which bird lays the biggest egg in the world?",
        "Answer": "The ostrich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the pouch in which marsupials carry their young?",
        "Answer": "The marsupium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the layer of the atmosphere closest to the earth's surface called?",
        "Answer": "The Troposphere"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nuclear process takes place in an atomic bomb?",
        "Answer": "Fission"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which bird can run the fastest?",
        "Answer": "Ostrich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only native North American marsupial?",
        "Answer": "The Opossum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What African animal kills the most people?",
        "Answer": "The Crocodile"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which leaves form the diet of the silkworm?",
        "Answer": "Mulberry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False: Sharks do not blink?",
        "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False: All polar bears are left-handed?",
        "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the condition of Nitrogen Embolism more commonly known as?",
        "Answer": "The bends"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented a vaccination for smallpox?",
        "Answer": "Edward Jenner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the more common name for the scapula?",
        "Answer": "The shoulder blade"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "An orchidectomy is the surgical removal of what?",
        "Answer": "Testicles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does LASER stand for?",
        "Answer": "Light Amplification by Stimulated Emission of Radiation"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does 'http' stand for, as used in website addresses?",
        "Answer": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to a cow that has not had a calf?",
        "Answer": "A Heifer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which is the only vitaman not to be found in an egg?",
        "Answer": "Vitamin C"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If a sow is a female pig, what is a male pig called?",
        "Answer": "A boar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mount Wilson in California, Siding Spring in Australia and Mauna Kea in Hawaii. What's the scientific connection?",
        "Answer": "They are astronomical observatories."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many claws does a house cat have?",
        "Answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If cats are 'feline', which animals are 'ovine'?",
        "Answer": "Sheep"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What word describes substances that can be broken down by biological action?",
        "Answer": "Biodegradable"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to the green alkaline fluid produced by the liver?",
        "Answer": "Bile"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the national flower of Austria?",
        "Answer": "Edelweiss"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where on the human body is the skin the thinnest?",
        "Answer": "Eyelids"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Sea Parrot is more usually known by which more common name?",
        "Answer": "Puffin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many eyes does a bee have?",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many pairs of chromosomes are there in the human body?",
        "Answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the art of clipping hedges into various shapes called?",
        "Answer": "Topiary"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the furthest planet from the sun?",
        "Answer": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the tallest grass in the world?",
        "Answer": "Bamboo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the first test tube baby born in 1978?",
        "Answer": "Louise Brown"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the human body, what are you born with 23 pairs of?",
        "Answer": "Chromosomes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the star Polaris better known?",
        "Answer": "The North Star"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the second NASA probe to land on Mars?",
        "Answer": "Opportunity"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only animal believed to hunt humans actively?",
        "Answer": "Polar Bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Carline, Meadow and Marsh are varieties of what?",
        "Answer": "Thistle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "September 27th 2005 marked the birthday of the search engine 'Google', but how many years old was it?",
        "Answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of a female donkey?",
        "Answer": "Jenny"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name for a group of goldfish? A troubling, a dole or a bloat?",
        "Answer": "A troubling"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At what gestation is a pregnancy classed full term? 27 weeks, 32 weeks or 37 weeks?",
        "Answer": "37 weeks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbo for Hydrogen?",
        "Answer": "H"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many sides has an octagon?",
        "Answer": "Eight"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If a dog is a canine and a cat a feline, what animal relates to a lupine?",
        "Answer": "Wolf"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only fish to have a prehensile tail?",
        "Answer": "A Seahorse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many inches of Mercury equal 1 Bar (1000 millibars)? 9.5, 19.5 or 29.5?",
        "Answer": "29.5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the three parts of the spine called?",
        "Answer": "Cervical, thoracic and lumbar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As in the saying 'once in a blue moon', what is a blue moon?",
        "Answer": "The second full moon that occurs in the same month."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "what is a molluscs tongue called? a chippel, a radula or an andilla?",
        "Answer": "radula"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bird in the world to have its nostrils at the tip of its long beak, just like a nose?",
        "Answer": "Kiwi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the acronym 'LASER' stand for?",
        "Answer": "Light Amplification through Stimulated Emission of Radiation"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is measured in Scoville Units?",
        "Answer": "The heat of chillies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is known as the father of geometry?",
        "Answer": "Euclid"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented the vulcanised rubber? Goodyear, Dunlop or Ford?",
        "Answer": "Goodyear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for the chemical ethanol? Alcohol, Ammonia or Citric Acid?",
        "Answer": "Alcohol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first man-made object to move faster than the speed of sound?",
        "Answer": "A whip"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the coloured part of an eye?",
        "Answer": "The iris"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many legs does a lobster have? Four, Eight or Ten?",
        "Answer": "Ten"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What musical bird can fly backwards?",
        "Answer": "The humming-bird"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What insect can also be known as the Devil's Darning Needle?",
        "Answer": "The Dragonfly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the craft in which John Glenn first orbited the Earth in 1962?",
        "Answer": "Friendship 7"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented the light bulb?",
        "Answer": "Thomas Edison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which part of the body is affected by Bright's disease?",
        "Answer": "The kidneys"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the initials 'PVC' stand for?",
        "Answer": "Polyvinyl chloride"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does a Gieger counter measure?",
        "Answer": "Radioactivity"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which part of the body would be treated by a chiropodist?",
        "Answer": "Feet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If a million is 10 to the power 6 then what is 10 to the power 18? one quadrillion, one trillion or one quintillion?",
        "Answer": "One quintillion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following metals is the best conductor of electricity? Copper, Platinum or Gold?",
        "Answer": "Copper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the closest star to Earth?",
        "Answer": "The sun"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The word 'cerebral' refers to which part of the body?",
        "Answer": "The brain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the famous equation E = MC squared, if 'E' stands for Energy and 'M' for Mass, what does 'c'' stand for?",
        "Answer": "The speed of light"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which annual prizes were established by the legacy of a Swedish chemist?",
        "Answer": "The Nobel Prizes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which planet in the Solar System does it constantly rain acid?",
        "Answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is mechanophobia the fear of? Machinery, Children or Paper?",
        "Answer": "Machinery"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many teeth make up a full adult set?",
        "Answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in your body would you find the anvil and the stirrup?",
        "Answer": "The ear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following could you use to measure how far you had walked? A Pedometer, A Cryometer or a Micrometer?",
        "Answer": "Pedometer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the fastest animal on 2 legs, which can reach a speed of around 40 miles per hour?",
        "Answer": "The ostrich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a female swan?",
        "Answer": "Pen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Orcinus Orca' is the Latin name for which sea creature?",
        "Answer": "Killer Whale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet was discovered in 1781 by Frederick Herschel?",
        "Answer": "Uranus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which recent computer virus was named after a popular female tennis player?",
        "Answer": "Kournikova"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "A female fox is known as a vixen, but what is a male fox known as?",
        "Answer": "A dog."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many noble gases are there?",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In astronomy, what are Pallas, Vesta and Davida?",
        "Answer": "Asteroids"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented the pneumatic tyre, which was first used on bicycles?",
        "Answer": "John Dunlop"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the average of the numbers 1, 10 and 100?",
        "Answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the ruling planet of the astrological sign Libra?",
        "Answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the plural of 'axis'?",
        "Answer": "Axes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1978, which European country became the first to ban aerosol sprays thought to damage the Ozone layer?",
        "Answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With what country are corgi dogs associated?",
        "Answer": "Wales"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'C' stand for in 'NICAM'? Compound, Companded or Co-acted?",
        "Answer": "Companded"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the condition of somnambulism better known?",
        "Answer": "Sleep-walking"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a taipan? A lizard, a snake or a beetle?",
        "Answer": "A snake"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which scientist was born in Germany in 1879, became a Swiss citizen in 1901 and later became a US citizen in 1940?",
        "Answer": "Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which metal has the chemical symbol Ag?",
        "Answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Hippomania is the name given to the obsession of which animals?",
        "Answer": "Horses"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Fermium? Fr, Fm or Fn?",
        "Answer": "Fm"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "A dipsomaniac would be obsessed with what?",
        "Answer": "Alcohol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many kidneys does a normal human have?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only common metal that is liquid at room temperature?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following planets is the smallest - Neptune, Earth or Mars?",
        "Answer": "Mars"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How often does Haley's comet appear?",
        "Answer": "Every 76 years"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many legs does an insect have?",
        "Answer": "Six"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who said 'The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mysterious. It is the source of all true art and science.'?",
        "Answer": "Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the plural of 'radius'?",
        "Answer": "Radii"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has a chemical symbol which does not begin with 'P'? Europium, Lead or Phosphorus?",
        "Answer": "Europium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Platinum?",
        "Answer": "Pt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Br?",
        "Answer": "Bromine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only mammal that can fly?",
        "Answer": "Bat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does NICAM stand for?",
        "Answer": "Near-Instantaneous Companded Audio Multiplexing"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which fruit is also known by the scientific name of 'Malus pumila'?",
        "Answer": "The apple"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What word is used to describe a group of ants?",
        "Answer": "Colony"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is a mandrill?",
        "Answer": "Monkey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the sum of the internal angles in a hexagon?",
        "Answer": "720 degrees"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is methyphobia the fear of?",
        "Answer": "Alcohol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is represented by the number 12 on the Beaufort Scale?",
        "Answer": "A hurricane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has the highest atomic number? Oxygen, Hydrogen or Helium?",
        "Answer": "Oxygen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "A koala bear eats leaves from which type of tree?",
        "Answer": "Eucalyptus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous British author wrote 'Chitty Chitty Bang Bang'?",
        "Answer": "Ian Fleming"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the hardest material in the human body?",
        "Answer": "Tooth enamel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has the atomic number 33? Arsenic, Zinc or Phosphorus?",
        "Answer": "Arsenic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Calcium?",
        "Answer": "Ca"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What constellation represents a hunter with club and shield?",
        "Answer": "Orion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the letters stand for in disease AIDS?",
        "Answer": "Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to an alloy of mercury?",
        "Answer": "Amalgam"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the longest bone in the human body?",
        "Answer": "The femur (thigh bone)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a female donkey called?",
        "Answer": "A jenny."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'Q' stand for in 'I.Q. Test'?",
        "Answer": "Quotient"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many arms does a starfish usually have?",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the national bird of New Zealand?",
        "Answer": "The Kiwi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is myrmecology the study of? Snakes, Ants or Bats?",
        "Answer": "Ants"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where are the smallest bones in the human body found?",
        "Answer": "Ear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "To the nearest whole number, how many revolutions does the moon make around the earth in a calendar year?",
        "Answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the planet closest to the Sun?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The chihauhau dog derives it's name from a town in which country?",
        "Answer": "Mexico."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many satellites does the planet Uranus have? 0, 5 or 15?",
        "Answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What quantity is measured in Amperes?",
        "Answer": "Electric current"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Hydrogen?",
        "Answer": "H"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following planets is the biggest - Earth, Uranus or Mars?",
        "Answer": "Uranus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does 5 on the Beaufort Scale represent? A fresh breeze, a light breeze or a near gale?",
        "Answer": "Fresh Breeze"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the tallest mammal?",
        "Answer": "The giraffe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the solar system, what is the third planet from the sun called?",
        "Answer": "Earth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do humans have 52 of in a lifetime, 20 of which are deciduous?",
        "Answer": "Teeth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to a young hare?",
        "Answer": "A leveret"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Fe?",
        "Answer": "Iron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Opium is derived from which plant?",
        "Answer": "Poppy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first man on the moon, and who was the second?",
        "Answer": "Neil Armstrong (1st) and Buzz Aldrin (2nd)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the first letter stand for in 'AC/DC'?",
        "Answer": "Alternating"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animal became extinct in Scotland in 1743 and then in Ireland in 1766?",
        "Answer": "The wolf."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is a natterjack?",
        "Answer": "A toad."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the more common name for the medical condition 'epistaxis'?",
        "Answer": "Nosebleed"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which temperature has the same value in both centigrade and farenheit?",
        "Answer": "-40"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which metallic element was known to the Romans as 'Plumbum'?",
        "Answer": "Lead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest mammal in the world and can reach a length of 100 foot?",
        "Answer": "The Blue Whale."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Iodine?",
        "Answer": "I"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the tallest and thickest kind of grass?",
        "Answer": "Bamboo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What did Nicholas Copernicus argue was at the centre of our universe, and what was the common belief before then?",
        "Answer": "The Sun. Before then people believed it was the Earth."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Pb?",
        "Answer": "Lead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What would you use an 'Endoscope' for?",
        "Answer": "Looking inside peoples bodies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was used to drive Charles Babbage's calculating machine which is regarded as the world's first computer? Electricity, Steam or Mice?",
        "Answer": "Steam"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a female peacock?",
        "Answer": "Peahen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Charon is the only satellite of which planet in the solar system?",
        "Answer": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Argon? Ar, Ag or An?",
        "Answer": "Ar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'V' stand for in DVD?",
        "Answer": "Versatile"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In degrees celcius, what is the normal body temperature?",
        "Answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the letter 'D' stand for in 'MS-DOS'? Data, Disk or Delivery?",
        "Answer": "Disk"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which gender of lion has a mane? The male, the female, or both?",
        "Answer": "Male"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What colour spots does a common ladybird have?",
        "Answer": "Black"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is xenophobia the fear of?",
        "Answer": "Foreigners"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which chemical element makes up 92.7% of the universe?",
        "Answer": "Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only fruit that grows its seeds on the outside?",
        "Answer": "The strawberry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Os?",
        "Answer": "Osmium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the ruling planet of the astrological sign Sagittarius?",
        "Answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Cornish, Rhode Island Red and Leghorn are all breeds of what?",
        "Answer": "Chicken"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the smallest planet in our Solar System?",
        "Answer": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Brontophobia is the fear of what? Thunder or Lightning?",
        "Answer": "Thunder"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1986, 9 moons of Uranus were discovered and named after what? Roman Gods, British Scientists or Shakesperian characters?",
        "Answer": "Shakesperian characters"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for the plant myosotis?",
        "Answer": "Forget-me-not"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does H.I.V. stand for?",
        "Answer": "Human Immunodeficiency Virus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The brightest star in the night sky and one of the closest to Earth is often called the Dog Star, but what is it's official name?",
        "Answer": "Sirius"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Nickel?",
        "Answer": "Ni"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What letter does not appear in the periodic table of the elements?",
        "Answer": "J"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does WYSIWYG stand for?",
        "Answer": "What you see is what you get"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to the fear of spiders?",
        "Answer": "Arachnophobia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to the young of a lion?",
        "Answer": "Cub"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is chromatics the science of?",
        "Answer": "Colours"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which part of the body is affected by conjunctivitis?",
        "Answer": "The eyes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has a chemical symbol which does not begin with 'A'? Silver, Gold or Tin?",
        "Answer": "Tin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only gemstone to be composed of one single element?",
        "Answer": "Diamond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet did Mariner 10 fly past and take pictures of in 1973?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest poisonous snake in Africa?",
        "Answer": "Black Mamba"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the fastest wild mammal in the UK?",
        "Answer": "The Roe Deer."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sn is the chemical symbol for which metallic element?",
        "Answer": "Tin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The peacock is the national bird of what country?",
        "Answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the periodic table, which element comes last alphabetically?",
        "Answer": "Zirconium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following planets has no moons? Mars, Earth or Mercury?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What would you measure with a protractor?",
        "Answer": "Angles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country does the wild dog, the dingo, live?",
        "Answer": "Australia."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to a female swan?",
        "Answer": "A pen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which scale would force 6 equal a strong breeze?",
        "Answer": "Beaufort"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which insects account for most deaths?",
        "Answer": "Mosquitos"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Achluophobia is the fear of what? Bright lights, flashing lights or the dark?",
        "Answer": "The dark"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What chemical element has the symbol Na?",
        "Answer": "Sodium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Equivalent to 3.26 light years, what is 'parsec' is an abbreviation of which two words?",
        "Answer": "Parallax second"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many species of elephant are there in the world?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On the beaufort scale, what number represents a fresh breeze? 1, 3 or 5?",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the gas Nitrous Oxide better known?",
        "Answer": "Laughing gas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Helium?",
        "Answer": "He"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the sixth planet from the Sun in the Solar System?",
        "Answer": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is ascorbic acid more commonly known?",
        "Answer": "Vitamin C"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has the highest atomic number? Lead, Xenon or Zirconium?",
        "Answer": "Lead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many days is the average gestation period of a rabbit? 30, 50 or 70?",
        "Answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to the young of a deer?",
        "Answer": "Fawn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the letters in the acronym LED stand for?",
        "Answer": "Light-emitting diode"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which infectious disease has a name derived from the Latin for 'bad air'?",
        "Answer": "Malaria"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1970, who landed the first wheeled vehicle on the moon? Russia or the America?",
        "Answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the most common gas in the air we breathe? Oxygen, Hydrogen or Nitrogen?",
        "Answer": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who discovered gravitation and invented calculus?",
        "Answer": "Isaac Newton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What company was once known as 'Quantum Computer Services Inc.'?",
        "Answer": "America Online"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If you were suffering from hepatitas which part of the body would be affected most?",
        "Answer": "The liver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where would you find budgerigars in their natural habitat? North Africa, The Far East or Australia?",
        "Answer": "Australia."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has the lowest atomic number? Silver, Calcium or Nitrogen?",
        "Answer": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animal is the source of cashmere?",
        "Answer": "The goat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is deoxyribonucleic acid better known as?",
        "Answer": "DNA"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Plutonium?",
        "Answer": "Pu"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which two continents do armadillos live?",
        "Answer": "North America and South America"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two metals make up the alloy bronze?",
        "Answer": "Copper and Tin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Is a group of crows called a murder, a massacre, a killing or a riot?",
        "Answer": "A murder"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol C?",
        "Answer": "Carbon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Strontium?",
        "Answer": "Sr"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female scientist was the first to win 2 Nobel Science prizes?",
        "Answer": "Marie Curie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the second lightest chemical element?",
        "Answer": "Helium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Carbon, Oxygen and which other element makes up carbohydrates?",
        "Answer": "Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What measurement is used to measure the size of horses?",
        "Answer": "Hands"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet has two moons called Phobos and Demos?",
        "Answer": "Mars"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a group of geese called?",
        "Answer": "A gaggle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Callisto, Europa, Ganymede and Io are 4 of the 16 moons of which planet?",
        "Answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Hg?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented penicillin in 1928?",
        "Answer": "Sir Alexander Fleming"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What disease's name comes from the Latin word for crab?",
        "Answer": "Cancer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of bird can swim the fastest?",
        "Answer": "The penguin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following would live in a formicary? Owls, bees or ants?",
        "Answer": "Ants"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a young bear?",
        "Answer": "A cub"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Cu?",
        "Answer": "Copper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for decompression sickness, a condition experienced by divers?",
        "Answer": "The bends"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is 'hi-fi' short for?",
        "Answer": "High-fidelity"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a male rabbit called?",
        "Answer": "A buck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which chemical element can take the form of diamond or graphite?",
        "Answer": "Carbon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What number on the Beaufort scale indicates a light breeze?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following species of snakes is the longest? Diamondback Rattlesnake, Reticulated Python or Puff Adder?",
        "Answer": "Reticulated Python"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When written out in full numerical form, how many zeros are in one centillion? 20, 100 or 600?",
        "Answer": "600"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol 'N'?",
        "Answer": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a male swan called?",
        "Answer": "Cob"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Death Cap, Shaggy Ink Cap and Stink Horn are all types of what?",
        "Answer": "Toadstools"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Oxygen and which other element makes up water?",
        "Answer": "Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet was not discovered until 1930?",
        "Answer": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the element Uranium named after?",
        "Answer": "The planet Uranus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Tin?",
        "Answer": "Sn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the smallest breed of dog?",
        "Answer": "Chihuahua"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does NASA stand for?",
        "Answer": "National Aeronautics and Space Administration"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing what does RAM stand for?",
        "Answer": "Random Access Memory"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the American use of the word 'trillion', how many zeros are there if this was written out in numerical form?",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the only two planets in the solar system which do not have moons?",
        "Answer": "Mercury and Venus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the more common name for Ethylene Glycol?",
        "Answer": "Antifreeze"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a baby frog called?",
        "Answer": "Froglet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is a modulator-demodulator better known as?",
        "Answer": "Modem"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is an Ishihara test used for?",
        "Answer": "To determine whether or not someone is colour blind."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has a chemical symbol which does not begin with 'S'? Sodium, Sulphur or Antimony?",
        "Answer": "Sodium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is oneirophobia the fear of? Children, Dreams or Blindness?",
        "Answer": "Dreams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the lighest element?",
        "Answer": "Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What animal is known as the ship of the desert?",
        "Answer": "The camel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What colour is cobalt?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What two-letter abbreviation in the computer industry stands for 1,048,576 bytes?",
        "Answer": "MB (for megabyte)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which is the eighth planet from the sun?",
        "Answer": "Neptune"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the most contagious disease in the world?",
        "Answer": "The common cold"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common name for sodium bicarbonate?",
        "Answer": "Baking Soda"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Other than humans, what are the only animals that have sex for pleasure?",
        "Answer": "Dolphins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does ASCII stand for in computing?",
        "Answer": "American Standard Code for Information Interchange"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What substance has the chemical formula C17 H21 O4 N?",
        "Answer": "Cocaine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many chambers does the heart have?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many eyes does a bee have? One, Four or Five?",
        "Answer": "Five"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Approximately how many muscles are there in the human body? 70, 700 or 7,000?",
        "Answer": "700"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the bone in a human's thigh?",
        "Answer": "Femur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name? Sun, Star or Moon?",
        "Answer": "Moon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following metallic elements has the lowest atomic number? Tin, Lead or Silver?",
        "Answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to the time of year when the sun is directly over the Equator at noon?",
        "Answer": "Equinox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What metallic element is the best conductor of electricity?",
        "Answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the space mission that saw the Russians send the dog 'Laika' into space?",
        "Answer": "Sputnik 2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In degrees Fahrenheit, what is the boiling point of water? 172, 212 or 252?",
        "Answer": "212"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What word is used to describe animals which can live on land or in water?",
        "Answer": "Amphibian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Barium? Ba, Bm or Bn?",
        "Answer": "Ba"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many pairs of ribs does a man have?",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The burning of what substance produces most of the world's electricity?",
        "Answer": "Coal"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Li?",
        "Answer": "Lithium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Ophidiophobia is the fear of what type of creatures?",
        "Answer": "Snakes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Zn?",
        "Answer": "Zinc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is trinitrotoluene better known?",
        "Answer": "TNT"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which organ of the human body does Hepatitis affect?",
        "Answer": "Liver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are commonly referred to as shooting stars?",
        "Answer": "Meteors"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What number on the Beaufort Scale represents a hurricane? 10, 12 or 14?",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is pathophobia the fear of? Illness, Lying or Memory Loss?",
        "Answer": "Illness"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was scientist Marie Curie?",
        "Answer": "Polish"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the medical condition of Lateral Epicondylitis more commonly known?",
        "Answer": "Tennis Elbow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the fear of horses called? Felophobia, Hippophobia or Equiphobia?",
        "Answer": "Hippophobia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the most common blood type in humans?",
        "Answer": "O"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the distinguishing feature of a Manx cat?",
        "Answer": "It has no tail"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The diameter of the Earth is approximately how many times bigger than the diameter of the Moon? 4, 24 or 104?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, how many nibbles are there in one byte?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol Po?",
        "Answer": "Polonium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are only three animals which walk by moving their front and hind legs on one side, then on the other?",
        "Answer": "Cat, Camel, Giraffe."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the young of a deer called?",
        "Answer": "A fawn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Oxygen?",
        "Answer": "O"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is cryophobia the fear of?",
        "Answer": "The cold"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False? An ostrich's eye is bigger than it's brain?",
        "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has the lowest atomic number? Mercury, Radium or Tungsten?",
        "Answer": "Tungsten"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of lions?",
        "Answer": "A pride"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the human body, what is the proper term for the thigh bone?",
        "Answer": "Femur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is 'Jerry's Guide to the World Wide Web' now known?",
        "Answer": "Yahoo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the distinctive feature of a Proboscis Monkey?",
        "Answer": "A long nose."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the medical name for the funny bone?",
        "Answer": "Humerus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many canine teeth does a human have?",
        "Answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two metallic elements form the alloy bronze?",
        "Answer": "Tin and Copper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the medical world, what do the initials ENT stand for?",
        "Answer": "Ear, Nose and Throat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What metal is also known as quicksilver?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What acid is extracted from the juice of lemons, oranges, limes, and grapefruit?",
        "Answer": "Citric"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In mathematics, what does the letter 'L' stand for in the abbreviation 'LCD'?",
        "Answer": "Lowest"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest land mammal in the world?",
        "Answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to a female horse aged four or under?",
        "Answer": "Filly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Neon?",
        "Answer": "Ne"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Gold?",
        "Answer": "Au"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What kind of animal is a saki?",
        "Answer": "Monkey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following does not mean the fear of surgery? Ergasiphobia, Tomophobia or Rupophobia?",
        "Answer": "Rupophobia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the difference between a frog and a toad?",
        "Answer": "A frog hops or leaps, while a toad walks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the four principal types of tooth called?",
        "Answer": "Incisors, Canines, Pre-molars and Molars."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1980 which electronics company demonstrated its latest invention, the compact disc?",
        "Answer": "Philips"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who shared a Nobel prize in 1945 for his discovery of the antibiotic penicillin?",
        "Answer": "Alexander Fleming"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sand consists of what two chemical elements?",
        "Answer": "Oxygen and Silicon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Is Sirius, which is also known as the Dog Star, the biggest, the brightest or the hottest star in the sky?",
        "Answer": "Brightest"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many stomachs does a cow have? None, Two or Four?",
        "Answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body would you find the malleus, incus and stapes?",
        "Answer": "In the ear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animal lives in a drey?",
        "Answer": "A squirrel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the most abundant metal in the earth's crust?",
        "Answer": "Aluminium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to an area is Space where the pull of gravity is so strong that nothing can escape it?",
        "Answer": "Black Hole."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the boiling point of water in degrees Fahrenheit?",
        "Answer": "212"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following planets has no moons? Neptune, Venus or Pluto?",
        "Answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the acronym ROM stand for?",
        "Answer": "Read Only Memory"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the main element found in steel? Tin, Iron or Lead?",
        "Answer": "Iron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which chemical element is most abundant in the air that we breathe?",
        "Answer": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who performed the first human heart transplant?",
        "Answer": "Dr Christiaan Barnard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British scientist originated the theory of evolution based on natural selection?",
        "Answer": "Charles Darwin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the traditional Christmas flower?",
        "Answer": "Poinsettia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body is the femur bone? The leg, the arm or the head?",
        "Answer": "Leg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many valves are there in the human heart?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many claws does a domestic cat have?",
        "Answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "10 to the power 0 is equal to what number?",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the smallest bird in the world?",
        "Answer": "The Bee Hummingbird"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In nature, what does a dendrologist study?",
        "Answer": "Trees"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a triangle where all sides are of different lengths and all angles of different size?",
        "Answer": "Scalene"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following is not a prime number? 319, 521 or 1033?",
        "Answer": "319"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does a cryometer measure? Air speed, low temperatures or the age of trees?",
        "Answer": "Low Temperatures"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does AC/DC stand for?",
        "Answer": "Alternating current / direct current"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the normal colour of sulphur?",
        "Answer": "Yellow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What number on the Beaufort scale represents a calm wind?",
        "Answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element is used in vulcanising rubber?",
        "Answer": "Sulphur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are Sirius, Vega and Rigal? Stars, Comets or Galaxies?",
        "Answer": "Stars"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the scientific term for the process of water turning to steam?",
        "Answer": "Evaporation"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the farenheit equivalent of 20 degrees centigrade?",
        "Answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only known substance that naturally exists on Earth in all three chemical states?",
        "Answer": "Water"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the English name for the constellation with the Latin name 'Ursa Major'?",
        "Answer": "Great Bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which vitamin is also known as tocopherol?",
        "Answer": "Vitamin E"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do edentulous mammals not have?",
        "Answer": "Teeth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was John Napier famous for inventing?",
        "Answer": "Logarithms"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the unofficial internet term for junk e-mail?",
        "Answer": "Spam"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What names are given to the male and to the female swan?",
        "Answer": "Cob (male) and Pen (female)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Claustrophobia is the fear of what?",
        "Answer": "Confined Spaces"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In diving, what does the letter 'C' stand for in 'Scuba'? Core, Controlled or Contained?",
        "Answer": "Contained"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has an atomic number less than 10? Beryllium, Phosphorus or Titanium?",
        "Answer": "Beryllium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'A' stand for in 'NICAM'?",
        "Answer": "Audio"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Radon? Ra, Rd or Rn?",
        "Answer": "Rn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what word comes from a contraction of the words 'by eight'?",
        "Answer": "Byte"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Do rattlesnakes lay eggs or have live babies?",
        "Answer": "They have live babies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Titan and Pandora are moons of which planet?",
        "Answer": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many bones are in a human neck? 2, 7 or 31?",
        "Answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is another name for a baby kangaroo?",
        "Answer": "A joey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest planet in the Solar System?",
        "Answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In centimeters, what is the diameter of a standard CD? 12, 14 or 16?",
        "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, if a byte is 8 bits, how many bits is a nibble?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the letter 'S' stand for in 'ASCII'?",
        "Answer": "Standard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many toes do camels have on each foot?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many bits are there in a byte?",
        "Answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which is the only planet in our Solar System that is not named after either a Greek or Roman God?",
        "Answer": "Earth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Carrots are especially rich in which vitamin?",
        "Answer": "Vitamin A"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the square root of one quarter?",
        "Answer": "One half"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a triangle with two sides the same length and two angles of equal size?",
        "Answer": "Isosceles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was Albert Einstein born?",
        "Answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The binary system of numbers uses which two numerical digits?",
        "Answer": "1 and 0"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the book 'A Brief History Of Time'?",
        "Answer": "Stephen Hawking"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body would you find the metatarsals?",
        "Answer": "In the feet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many millions away from the Sun is the Earth? 93 million, 2 and a half billion, or 113 billion?",
        "Answer": "93 million"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What number on the Beaufort scale represents a storm?",
        "Answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the sum of the internal angles in a hexagon?",
        "Answer": "720"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'A' stand for in the disease 'AIDS'?",
        "Answer": "Acquired"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of creature is a kookaburra?",
        "Answer": "Bird"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many prime numbers are there between 10 and 20?",
        "Answer": "Four (11, 13, 17 and 19)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the letter 'C' stand for in the acronymp BASIC? Code, Company or Computing?",
        "Answer": "Code"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the English name for the constellation with the Latin name 'Hydrus'?",
        "Answer": "Water Snake"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What medical term evolved as a result of a condition suffered by Chang and Eng Bunker?",
        "Answer": "Siamese Twins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is a flying fox? A fish, a bat or a squirrel?",
        "Answer": "Bat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many carats are there in pure gold?",
        "Answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many zeros would you associate with the metric prefix 'giga'?",
        "Answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who became the first American to orbit the Earth in 1962 and returned to Space in 1997?",
        "Answer": "John Glenn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following letters does not feature in the chemical formula for water? C, H or O?",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following animals have fingerprints that are very similar to human fingerprints? Chimpanzees, Koala Bears or Possums?",
        "Answer": "Koala Bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet was discovered in 1930 and has only one known satellite called Charon?",
        "Answer": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only venomous mammal in the world?",
        "Answer": "The duckbill platypus."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only mammal which can't jump?",
        "Answer": "The Elephant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the more common name for the disease 'Rubella'?",
        "Answer": "German Measles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only animal which, for both genders, is born with horns on its forehead?",
        "Answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is the domesticated albino variety of polecat better known?",
        "Answer": "Ferret"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Equus is the latin name for what animal?",
        "Answer": "Horse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of kangaroos? An army, a mob or a troop?",
        "Answer": "A mob"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has the atomic number 2? Carbon, Lithium or Helium?",
        "Answer": "Helium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Masked, Hermit and Spider are all types of which animal?",
        "Answer": "Crab"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How does a python snake kill its prey?",
        "Answer": "By constricting them"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two planets are the only ones in our solar system to have no moons?",
        "Answer": "Venus and Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only mammal that can fly?",
        "Answer": "The bat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which plant is the only one to have flowers, but no proper leaves?",
        "Answer": "Cactus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the world's first cloned sheep?",
        "Answer": "Dolly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol P?",
        "Answer": "Phosphorus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What single letter is the chemical symbol for the element Potassium?",
        "Answer": "K"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the medical condition of myopia better known as?",
        "Answer": "Short-sightedness"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Britain's first nuclear powered submarine?",
        "Answer": "HMS Dreadnought"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of creature is a taipan?",
        "Answer": "Snake"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who said 'Science without religion is lame. Religion without science is blind'?",
        "Answer": "Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Chinese and the Mississippi are the only two known species of which creature?",
        "Answer": "Alligator"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "A Griffin has the head of which type of bird?",
        "Answer": "Eagle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Excluding the sun, what is the name of the nearest star to Earth?",
        "Answer": "Proxima Centauri"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The speed of light is approximately equal to how many miles per second? 186,000, 6.1 million or 310 million?",
        "Answer": "186,000"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the mission that involved the first manned lunar landing in 1969?",
        "Answer": "Apollo XI"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which metal is the best conductor of electricity?",
        "Answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does MS-DOS stand for?",
        "Answer": "Microsoft Disk-Operating System"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following is not a moon of the planet Jupiter? Elera, Mimas or Carme?",
        "Answer": "Mimas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the human body is the labyrinth?",
        "Answer": "The ear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False: In space it is impossible to cry:?",
        "Answer": "True (there is no gravity, so tears can't flow)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False: Slug's don't have noses?",
        "Answer": "False (they have four!)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective name for a group of insects?",
        "Answer": "A swarm"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If the cheetah is the fastest thing on four legs, what is the fastest on two legs?",
        "Answer": "The Ostrich."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element forms 80% of the Earth's atmosphere?",
        "Answer": "Nitrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What two colours are the stripes on a Colorado beetle?",
        "Answer": "Yellow and Black"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol As?",
        "Answer": "Arsenic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which number is written 1010 in binary?",
        "Answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to the home of an otter?",
        "Answer": "A holt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which mammals have prehensile tails?",
        "Answer": "Monkeys"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "To the nearest whole number, how many metres is 20 feet?",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does CPU stand for?",
        "Answer": "Central processing unit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bird that can swim but not fly?",
        "Answer": "The penguin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the body can you find your metacarpal bones?",
        "Answer": "In your hands"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following elements has a chemical symbol which does not begin with 'I'? Iodine, Iron or Iridium?",
        "Answer": "Iron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to someone who studies plants?",
        "Answer": "Botanist"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In maths what name is given to the series of numbers where each number is the sum of the previous two?",
        "Answer": "Fibonacci Series"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'S' stand for in 'NASA'? Space, Science or Society?",
        "Answer": "Space"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many wings does a normal bee have?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'spam', the internet term for sending unsolicited e-mail, what does the letter 'p' stand for? Personl, People or Permission?",
        "Answer": "People"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the highest melting point?",
        "Answer": "Carbon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What two different types of camel are there?",
        "Answer": "Dromedary and Bactrian."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only venomous snake in Britain?",
        "Answer": "The adder."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol S?",
        "Answer": "Sulphur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of dogs are commonly kept by Eskimos?",
        "Answer": "Huskies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which flower does the spice saffron come from?",
        "Answer": "Crocus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented the Centigrade scale of temperature?",
        "Answer": "Anders Celcius"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is tocophobia the fear of? Travelling by train, drowning or childbirth?",
        "Answer": "Childbirth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Approximately what percentage of the human body is water? 60%, 70% or 80%",
        "Answer": "0.8"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On the Beaufort Scale of wind speed what comes after a fresh breeze?",
        "Answer": "Strong Breeze"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who invented the television?",
        "Answer": "John Logie Baird"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which controversial issue was Doctor Jack Kevorkian associated?",
        "Answer": "Euthanasia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the US space station Skylab launched?",
        "Answer": "1973"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Isihara Plate tests are used to determine what?",
        "Answer": "Colour Blindness"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is a sidewinder?",
        "Answer": "A snake (desert rattlesnake)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the letter 'B' stand for in the acronym BASIC? Beginners, Boolean or Basic?",
        "Answer": "Beginners"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many legs does a spider have?",
        "Answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bird which hunts by the sense of smell?",
        "Answer": "The kiwi."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name is given to the young of a horse?",
        "Answer": "Foal"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what names are the constellations Corona Australis and Corona Borealis better known?",
        "Answer": "Southern Crown and Northern Crown."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the medical name for the small channel between your top lip and your nose?",
        "Answer": "Philtrum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the scientific name for the wind pipe?",
        "Answer": "The trachea"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which gas is often referred to as laughing gas?",
        "Answer": "Nitrous Oxide"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only animal to have four knees?",
        "Answer": "The elephant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a young goat?",
        "Answer": "A kid"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What would a Geiger counter be used to measure?",
        "Answer": "Radiation"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the four categories of taste that the human tongue can detect?",
        "Answer": "Sweet, Sour, Salt and Bitter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is an anenometer used to measure?",
        "Answer": "Wind Speed"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a young whale?",
        "Answer": "A calf"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a chuckwalla? A lizard, a turtle or an antelope?",
        "Answer": "A lizard."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the more common name for the condition of 'otalgia'?",
        "Answer": "Earache"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where might you come across a polar bear? At the north or south pole?",
        "Answer": "North pole"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of whales?",
        "Answer": "A school"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two elements make up Ammonia?",
        "Answer": "Nitrogen and Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is a polygraph better known?",
        "Answer": "Lie detector test"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Voyager 2 discovered 6 moons of which planet in August 1989?",
        "Answer": "Neptune"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is another name for the mountain lion?",
        "Answer": "Puma"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of bean is the ingredient for baked beans?",
        "Answer": "Harricot"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the letter 'O' stand for in 'MS-DOS'?",
        "Answer": "Operating"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a flying fox? A bat, a fish or a lizard?",
        "Answer": "A bat."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which vitamin improves the eye's ability to see in the dark?",
        "Answer": "Vitamin A"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the initials IBM stand for?",
        "Answer": "International Business Machines"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Lentigines is the medical term for what? Birthmarks, freckles or fingernails.",
        "Answer": "Freckles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many legs does an ant have?",
        "Answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is a 'motmot'?",
        "Answer": "A bird"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Bauxite is the ore of which element?",
        "Answer": "Aluminium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the disease caused by lack of vitamin C?",
        "Answer": "Scurvy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Chemically pure gold contains how many carats?",
        "Answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the four main blood groups?",
        "Answer": "A, B, AB and O"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "White Admiral and Camberwell Beauty are different types of what creature?",
        "Answer": "Butterfly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet in the Solar System is closest in size to Earth?",
        "Answer": "Venus."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃÅwwwÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢ stand for?",
        "Answer": "World Wide Web"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, which operating system has a penguin as it's logo?",
        "Answer": "Linux"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which of the following was the Frenchman Fourier best known? Chemistry, Biology or Mathematics?",
        "Answer": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Cats are indigenous to all but which two continents?",
        "Answer": "Australia and Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following is not a moon of the planet Jupiter? Ananke, Callisto or Bianca?",
        "Answer": "Bianca"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is an eland? An antelope, a monkey or a bat?",
        "Answer": "An antelope."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of toads? A knot, a stitch or a weave?",
        "Answer": "A knot"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the English name for the constellation with the Latin name 'Mensa'?",
        "Answer": "Table"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of monkeys?",
        "Answer": "A troop"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which chemical element is derived from the Greek word for 'male'?",
        "Answer": "Arsenic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What word can be used to describe a group of Kangaroos or Baboons?",
        "Answer": "A troop"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is a group of chickens called?",
        "Answer": "A brood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is a Bombay Duck?",
        "Answer": "Fish"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the plural of mongoose?",
        "Answer": "Mongooses"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element spontaneously ignites in normal air?",
        "Answer": "Phosphorous"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many tentacles does an Octopus have?",
        "Answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which has the larger ears - the African or Asian elephant?",
        "Answer": "African"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who first argued that the world was not flat?",
        "Answer": "Aristotle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What element was the chemical symbol 'Y'?",
        "Answer": "Yttrium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In computing, what does the letter 'A' stand for in 'ASCII'? All, Assumed or American?",
        "Answer": "American"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is zoophobia the fear of?",
        "Answer": "Animals"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element was used to make brass, but not recognised as a separate metal until 1746?",
        "Answer": "Zinc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following is not a moon of the planet Saturn? Titan, Juliet or Pandora?",
        "Answer": "Juliet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Uranium? U, Ur or Un?",
        "Answer": "U"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Is a substance with a pH value less than 7 known as an acid or an alkali?",
        "Answer": "Acid"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the smallest planet in the Solar System?",
        "Answer": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the collective noun for a group of rhinoceroses? A strike, a blow or a crash?",
        "Answer": "A crash"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Approximately what percentage of the human body is water? 27%, 63% or 80%?",
        "Answer": "80%"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Ascorbic acid also known as what Vitamin?",
        "Answer": "Vitamin C"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two elements make up the alloy brass?",
        "Answer": "Copper and Zinc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is trichology the study of? Hair, Bones or Fingernails?",
        "Answer": "Hair"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of clouds produce rain or snow? Cirrus, Cumbulus or Nimbus?",
        "Answer": "Nimbus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a young lion?",
        "Answer": "A cub"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in the body would you find the femur bone?",
        "Answer": "The leg (thigh bone)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What animal has the heavist and most complex brain in the animal world?",
        "Answer": "The sperm whale."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which organ in the human body regulates the amount of water in the blood and helps remove waste products?",
        "Answer": "Kidney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Acid rain is caused by what polluting gas?",
        "Answer": "Sulphur Dioxide"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mariner 10 is the only space probe to fly past which planet, sending back pictures showing it to resembling the Earth's moon?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which element has the chemical symbol P?",
        "Answer": "Phosphorous"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the sum of the internal angles of any triangle?",
        "Answer": "180 degrees"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only bird which hunts by the sense of smell? The Kiwi, The Condor or The Ostrich?",
        "Answer": "Kiwi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name given to a young eagle?",
        "Answer": "An eaglet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which is the fastest land mammal?",
        "Answer": "The cheetah"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many days is the average gestation period of a mouse? 3, 11 or 21?",
        "Answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What single letter is the chemical symbol for the element Tungsten?",
        "Answer": "W"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What method of transport did Christopher Cockerell patent in 1955?",
        "Answer": "Hovercraft"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What number on the Beaufort scale represents a moderate wind?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the Mohs scale measure?",
        "Answer": "The hardness of solids."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What two metals are the most commonly used to conduct electricity in homes?",
        "Answer": "Copper and Aluminium"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the medical condition dyspepsia better known?",
        "Answer": "Indigestion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the second largest planet in the Solar System?",
        "Answer": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What defines the measurement of a light year?",
        "Answer": "The distance that light travels in a year"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which continent does the zebra come from?",
        "Answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which is larger - the Indian or African elephant or are they both the same size?",
        "Answer": "African"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element Silver?",
        "Answer": "Ag"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'M' is the ruling planet of the astrological sign Gemini?",
        "Answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest joint in the human body?",
        "Answer": "The knee joint"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Used in mathematics, what is the value of Pi to three decimal places?",
        "Answer": "3.142"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which planet in the solar system would come third alphabetically?",
        "Answer": "Mars"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What fraction of an iceberg is exposed above the water? one third, one seventh or one eleventh?",
        "Answer": "One eleventh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Sun is mainly composed of Hydrogen and which other gas?",
        "Answer": "Helium"
    }
]